Our Privacy Policy
------------------

We respect and honor your privacy! Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to Chaos Software Group, Inc. will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to [let us know](https://www.chaossoftware.com/contact.aspx).

1. **We use secured servers.**  
    Your personal information provided through our online store is fully secured and protected through Secure Socket Layers (SSL). All of your personal information such as your name, email address, and credit card number are encrypted and made unintelligible to hackers.
2. **We do not sell, rent, lease, or supply your personal information to any third parties.**  
    It is common in this day and age to buy a product or supply an email address and then to receive significant amounts of unrelated mail from third parties who have obtained your information from the place you made your purchase. Unlike the norm, we guard your information and do not sell it, rent it, lease it, or otherwise supply it to anyone else for any purpose.
3. **All information provided to us is considered confidential.**  
    Any personal information provided in our online store is used ONLY for processing your order. We will not call or contact you by mail in the future, nor use the information you provide for any purpose other than adding you to our own low-traffic announcement email list if you opt-in or choose to be added to it.
4. **We would never intentionally send our customers unsolicited emails.**  
    Users who make a purchase from our online store or who specifically request to be subscribed are added to our Chaos Software Group email announcement mailing list. All emails come specifically from us - we do not share or sell our email lists with anyone but guard them as an important company asset. This list is not a high-traffic list. You will be send an announcement from us only when we have something we feel is significant to our users . Our email list is also very easy to "opt-out" of to remove yourself from future communications, should you choose to do so.
5. **Personal Cookies we create and use are destroyed automatically.**  
    Browser "cookies" used to remember your progress while making purchases in our online store and are destroyed automatically at the end of your browser session. These "purchase" cookies NEVER contain your credit card information. Nothing temporarily stored in a "purchase" cookie is available to any other sites on the Internet.

This privacy statement covers our policy for [https://www.chaossoftware.com](https://www.chaossoftware.com/), formerly http://www.isbister.com.

Our site does contains links to other sites for which we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of.

* * *

**Resale or disclosure of information to third parties:**

Chaos Software does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including membership forms or email lists.

**Browser information collected on the website:**

Our Chaos Software web site administrator analyzes our website logs to constantly improve the value of the materials available on website. Our website logs **are not personally identifiable**, and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site.

**Use of cookies:**

Any browser "cookies" used on our site for purchases are destroyed automatically at the end of your browser session. We use cookies to track the progress of your purchases in our online store. They NEVER contain your credit card information. Nothing temporarily stored in a purchase cookie is available to any other sites on the Internet.

**Privacy of our email lists:**

Chaos Software maintains an email list to keep customers and interested members of the general public informed about software updates or breaking news. Individuals must affirmatively request to join our mailing lists by signing up through a form on our web site or by purchasing software through our online secure store. We do not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease the addresses on our list to anyone. In addition, we configure our list server software to refuse to divulge the email addresses of our list subscribers to anyone but authorized Chaos Software Group, Inc. staff, including other list subscribers.

**Your Choice/Opt-Out options**

The only use of your personal information other than to process purchases is to be placed on our announcement email list. Announcements are only sent by Chaos Software, never by other companies. Although receiving information about new products and updates can be valuable to users, this site gives users the options for removing their information from our email list to not receive future communications from us.

* You can visit the following URL for instructions to remove your email address from our announcement mailing list: [https://www.chaossoftware.com/maillist.aspx](https://www.chaossoftware.com/maillist.aspx)

**Your Correct/Update options**

Should users need to correct or update information previously provided, use the Contact Us web form at [https://www.chaossoftware.com/contact.aspx](https://www.chaossoftware.com/contact.aspx)

**Third Party Tracking and Advertising**

Our website has removed tracking services from third party vendors, including Google, so they will no longer track usage of our website anonymously.

**Contacting Chaos Software Group, Inc.**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at [https://www.chaossoftware.com/contact.aspx](https://www.chaossoftware.com/contact.aspx) or:

Chaos Software Group, Inc.  
PO Box 865154  
Plano, TX 75086-5154

**Effective Date**

This policy statement was originally created and put into effect on July 23, 1999. It was updated on January 11, 2013 to reflect our removal of third party vendors for anonymous cookie use and our updated mailing address.  
  
This policy is based on principles followed by our company since our founding in 1991.

Copyright © 2024 Chaos Software Group, Inc.  -  All Rights Reserved

\[ [Home](https://www.chaossoftware.com/index.aspx) \] \[ [Products and Downloads](https://www.chaossoftware.com/products.aspx) \] \[ [ChaosHost.com](https://www.chaoshost.com/) \] \[ [Labs](https://www.chaossoftware.com/chaos-labs.aspx) \] \[ [Chaos University](https://www.chaossoftware.com/university/) \] \[ [Mailing List](https://www.chaossoftware.com/maillist.aspx) \] \[ [Purchase](https://www.chaossoftware.com/store.aspx) \] \[ [Sales](https://www.chaossoftware.com/sales.aspx) \] \[ [Support](https://www.chaossoftware.com/support/) \] \[ [Privacy](https://www.chaossoftware.com/privacy.aspx)\]
